谨以此片追忆逝去的童年，如果你也有这样的童年的话欢迎加入我们的贴吧"神剑传奇"。本作品之片源来自互联网，版权归原公司所有。任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途，一切后果由该组织或个人承担！制作者不承担任何法律及连带责任！请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
F
2.∈
△ n Productions XIl Ing
FRance 2. Et(ipse Animatino02
F
2.∈
FRance 2. Ecipse Animat ion. Tooncan Productions Xll Inc
翻译：英语辅导频道
输入/时间轴/压制：harry159821/黑月
F△nc2.∈per
D
Dominique
pt oy
D
ominique La
校对：
Go on! Move
快点过去
I want to see
everyone in the square
我要在广场上见到所有入
Don't be afraid
they'lI soon be gone
别害怕他们很快动
【
Bring out all your provisions
and no harm will come to you!
所有粮食交出来我们就不会动你们
You would take everything?
你们要抢走所有粮食
And let oura
entire illage starve?
让我们所有的村民挨饿吗
The strong will survive.
强者生存
hat's the law
of nature, tavern-keeper
那可是自然规律酒馆老板
and the law of
the People of the sea
也是海上枭雄的生存法则
This gives me the right
拳头给了我权利
Understood?
懂吗
That's better!
好多了
That's everything
almost too much to carr
西克都在那了多得可能搬不动了
第？集
Good! Make the villagers help
不错那叫村民们帮忙
I don' t want the
bother of coming back
我可不希望回去还有什么麻烦
Look! Here comes the
runt, and his bodyguards
瞧瞧矮子和他的保镖来了
I think you and your
men will be leaving now.
我想你和你的人会马上离开
though you may want-to apologise
first for frightening these people.
而且首先你要为惊吓了这里的人道歉
≡
Did you hear that?
你们听到了没
Youe think I'm afraid
of an apprentice Shog
你认为我会害怕
boys-asguadde ue Jo
聊看的斗
ladde ue」o
You think I'mafraid
of an apprentices Shogi
以为我稳
who hides behind women?
个躲在女背后的实习法师吗
You're the brave
one
riatt Zek
你
It takes a lot of courage
带着帮匙来掠夺
的村民
to lead a band of warriors
into a defenceless village
是需要很大的勇气吧
么
Herik!
哈里克你没事吧
So the little Shogi is angry!
看样子小术士
Lets let them settle
this fairly shall we?
谁他们公更解决吧如何
It's alright. Djana
take care of them
我没事裘娜我会招呼他们
Don't push-me, Zek Got it?
要推我西克听到没
sndyauog
据
Dont push merek Got it?
hhat's enough
You've both shown
what great fighters you are
你们俩可都是多么伟大的勇士
This isn't going
o settle anything
这样解不了任何问题
You're right, Djana
你说得对裘
But you and your men
will leave the village, now
你和你的人现在马上离开村子
Well be back, princes
我们会再来的公主殿下
All right, men! Were leaving
你们听到没现在撤
And I'm coming with you!
我跟你一起走
Herik?>
哈里克你想干
You heard him, Djana
你也听到他说了裘娜
They'll just raid
again when we' re not around
我们不在附近的时候他们还会来的
here or somewhere else
抢劫这里或者其他地方
Unless we stop it once and for
除非我们次解决这个题以防后患
4 What's with Herik?
哈里克怎么了
Does he want another
shot at Zek that bad?
他想和西克再干二架吗
He's got a score to settle,
<Wip, but not with Zek
他这样做有他的理由威普
但是不是为了西克
是不是为了西克
过 Like I said,youe
taking me with you
就如我刚才所说你们带上我
want to speak to -wolf
我想找Q尔夫谈谈
And so do
我也去
No. Djana! I prefer
to handle this myself!
不要娜我想自己解决这件事
Let him do it his way. Djae
他照自已的方式去做吧裘
Wolf doesnot
respondewell to demands
尔夫向来不屑理睬别人的要求
Besides, I think it would be
etter for us to stay herea
简我想我们最好留在里
and make sure that Zek's men
确定西克和他的人
p
awa
the village
真的离开村子
All right. since, both
you seem to agree
既然你们两个都么说那行
Be firm.Herik
坚决点哈里克
our father will only listen
you if he respects you.
如亲尊重你他才会接受你的意见
Find a horse for Zek, Pavel.
帮西克找匹马来帕维尔
It wouldn't be right for the great
conqueror of defenceless villagers
总不能让掠夺手无寸铁村民的伟征服者
ato leade Herik on foot!
和里克步行前往吧
且
don't like seeing you
go off alone with Zek
我不想让你独自一个人跟西克去
Don't worry. we Shogis have!.
a few tricks up our sleeves
别担心我们三基寺法师自有妙计
He's in no danger
他不会有危险的
Zek might/ boast and brag
and throw a punch or two
虽然西克会自吹自擂还出手打
but heid- never risk really
hurting the son of his chiet
但他绝不会正伤害到他首领的儿
Isn't that right
我说的不对吗
Watch your back, Herik
自己小心哈里克
Watch you论里克
Give it to me
巴它给我
Dont you think we have enough
problems with. the Bar.barian
你们还这样难道蛮族人的事不够头疼吗
with the People of the Sea?
恩我是指海上枭雄
He.- refuses to
give me back my grain
他不肯把谷子还给我
He's always
他老是这
He's just stubborn
He knows th
Enoug
他明知道这袋谷是我的够了
One at a time!
兑
You first
先
Well, after you
chased away the Bar
在您赶走蛮族人
三
the Men of the Sea
赶走海上枭雄之后
each villager took his
own-goods back from/ the pile
村民们从谷堆里拿走了各自的谷子
This_is the last bag of grain
这是最后一袋谷
So. whose is it?
那这是谁的
Mine! Mi
是我的我的
see: a- question of property.
明自了财产归属问题
It's up to the lord of the land
to settle this kind of dispute
应该由你们领地的主人来解决这个回题
But this bag belongs to me!
可这袋谷子是我的
Prince Duncan is away, Djana
邓肯亲王现在外出了裘娜
- There's no one else at hand
with=the authority to make a ruling
没有其他人有权利做出判决
Except for you, Princes
除了你公主殿下
除了我
Me?
You are a Lord
您是殿下
Well, a Lady
Lady
王
wWell. a Lady
恩是位公主
Wel
L
小主
And you carry the Sword of Justice
而且您佩带着正义之剑
That's right. You can decide
由您来定
写
Wolf
你夫
wolf
沃尔夫
Wolf
wolf
沃尔夫
Where are the provisions
And the- men
供给带回来了没有其他人呢
Your men will
be-here soon. Wolf.
尔夫三你的大很快就到
But-as for-suppliesp you'll
haveto find another source
至宇供给我想你得男我了
Don't think
you can defy me, Herik
哈里克不要以为是我儿子
just because you are my son!
然反抗我
rdon't expect-any thing
rom my fathe
沃尔夫饿没期望能从父亲那得到什么
came to speak to the leader
f the People of the Sea
我是来技海上一族首领谈谈
And I still say you cannot
continue to pillage the kingdom
我想说你不能继续掠夺王国的子民
Your son is a true Shogi, Wolf
天尔夫你儿子可是位真正的法
Just like his mother
就跟他母亲―样
么
You will not speak of her, Zek
不要提到她西克
Leave us alone
我们单独呆会
Both of you!
们两都离开
What about me, father?
May I speak of my/mother?
父亲我可以提到我母亲么
Come. it's time we had a talk
来吧是时候该我们好好谈谈了
F
First it's the mothe
and now it's the son
先是母亲现在是儿子
putting strange
ideas in Wolfs head!
把些奇怪的想法装进了沃尔夫的脑子里
I should have killed both of
them when I had the chance!
上次我就应该把他们两个都干
Alas, /that opportunity is past, Zek
可惜你错失了那次机会西克
But we may have another-s
不过我们也许另有良材
You are the keeper of
our tradition, Zoldan
佐登你是我们传统的守护者
If you can help me protect our
-way-of life, even from our chief.
你能帮我保持我们原有的生活方式吧
甚至是反抗我们的首领
It is your duty to do so
你有责任这么做
Spirits of the air and
f time, inspire my vision
空气和时间之神请开启我的天眼吧
Ugh, magic!
又是什么巫术
Nothing solves a problem
more than a sharp blade
没什么能比利剑更能解决问题了
You again, little shaman!
又是你小萨满
Oh, master of darkness
hear my request.
噢黑暗之王我有一个请求
I call on you to
我请求你
Enough of your babbling
不要再喋喋不休了
and most of our
warriors are on land
而且我们大部分武士还都在岸上
He could be taken very easily.
要抓到他真是轻而易举
I see Barbarians are far more
skilled at treachery than flattery
看来蛮族人不仅懂得阿谀奉承
更擅长变节啊
will send Bragan, the Regent
我会把摄政王布拉刚叫来
Do not let the Shogi slip
through you fingers before he arrive
在他赶过来之前别让小术士跑了
召备形e号
出
It was so long age
是很久以前的事了
yet I remember
that day so clearly
可那一天还很清晰地在我脑海里
ek brought me a Shogi
西克抓到一位法师他带她来见我
who claimed to be a
messenger from the Shogi Master
那位法师自称是大法师的信使
but Zek believed
his prisoner was a spy
可西克坚信他的阶下囚是间谍
▲
Is this how the Peoplemof the Sea
greet those who come in peace?
海上枭雄就是这么对待和平使者的吗
bring you a chance for
better life for your people.
我给你带来一个良机可以
你的子民生活得好
Don't throw it away
不要把我的话抛之脑后
李
That first encounter
was a bit-unusua
我们的第一次相遇有点不寻常
t but then, your mother was
an extraordinary woman, Herik
你母亲是位特别的女性哈里克
My mother was a Sho
我母亲是一位法师吗
The Shogi Master never told-mel
大法师从来没跟我说过
He must have thought it better
that you didn't know, as did,
如同我所想他肯定也是认
不让你知道更好
But it's never bette
可没有比这更糟糕的
Get us under way without delay
朝目标前进一刻也不准耽搁
Then prepare a boarding party
然后准备一个登船仪式
We're off on a hunt!
我们马上抓捕猎物
自
D
Look at how oily these stems are!
看那些稻杆上面多油腻啊
So this is the grainein the bag
这和袋子里的谷子出自同三个地方
That's- where sitmis-stored
谷就是堆在那的
My grain is of much
uality than h
我家谷子比他家的好多
What should do. Tara?
我该怎么办塔拉
What? You're asking me?
仕么你在问我
Far be it for a
lowly commoner like me
这和重要的事情可不是
象我这样地位卑微的平民
to\ a lady
oni such weighty matters
可以给公主您提供建议的啊
think I'd better
oin Wip at the tavern.
我想我最好上酒馆找威普去
That fangor stew
really looked delicious
那个炖梵高真的看起来很美味哦
Your modesty is truly inspiring
你的谦虚真让人受鼓舞
thank you so much for your help
实在要感谢你帮忙
Katryn-tried to persuade
us to change our ways
凯塞茵试图说服我们改变原来的生活方式
She began with me
于是她从我这里着手开始
For the first time in
my life, I was vulnerable.
我生平第一次那么容易被影响了
She was a shogi, an enemy
opposed to our way, of life
池是个法师还是我的敌人
而且还反对我们的生活方式
and yet I could not muster
any hostility towards her
可对她我找不到一丝敌意
say we kill her.
to- example
我说杀了她一以敬效尤
To show them that
we cannot be trick
诉他们我们不会中
to have your own
place in his kingdom
可以让你们在他的王国里有个容身之处
You are very
sure of yourself, Shogi.
你说得可填真有把握法师A
You are very
三、你说得可真有状法师
I were not. I wouldn't be here
如果不确信这点我就不会在这里
二
Turn around
转过身
Katryn truly admired our ability to
make use of the ocean's resources
凯塞茵非常钦佩我们刘
海洋资源的利用
She believed we could develop a
thriving trade with the continent
她相信我们可以与大陆上
的居民进荷繁荣的交易
not as savages
而不是把我们当野蛮大
She convinced?
她让我信用子
证二
Iwill-never forget
lowI felt- about her.
我永远不会忘记当时我对她的感觉
What happened?"
后来怎样
Many among my people could
not accept my love for a Shogi
族里
不能接受我爱上一个法师
When you were born, Herik.
my happiness was unbound
里克你出生后二我感觉幸福极了
Katryn had given
me
son an heir
凯塞茵帮我生了个元字生了企继承
I was sure that with time
my men would accept you
当时我相信时间长了族人就会接受你
=
You were my/son.
consecrated by our(people's rites
你是我儿子得到了族里神圣仪式的认可
You were a Man of the sea
你是海上枭雄的一份子
A
But they never
did accept me, did they?
可他们从没真正接受我对吧
You sent me away
后来你把我送走了
No, Herik -your.mother
ed and took you away.
哈里克是你母亲把你一起带走了
Back to the cursed- Shogis
and away from your people
回到那群该死的法师中间
让你离开了你的子民
Away from me
也离开了
Dont worry
Everything will be all right
别担心一切都会顺利的
h.|…know= Herik
can take care of himse
我知道哈里克可以照顾好自已
I wasn' t talking about Herik
我说的不是哈里克
was thinking about the grain
dispute thatyou have to settle
而是指你要解决的那袋谷子的归属问题
Yes, of course. A bag of grain
是的没错谷子的归属问题
seems so silly
看起来真可笑
I was half-kidding when said
they should take it up/with Duncun
当时我他们找双肯解决是半开元笑的
I wonder what he'd say
我想他会说什么呢
He would take it very seriously
他会很认真解决这件事的
A bag of grain may
seem, silly to a princes
争夺一袋谷子对一位公主来说
确实很可笑
but it means a lot to
people who don't have), much
可对穷人来说却意味着很多
You're right of course
你确实说对
Still.I think I should
have gone with Herik
要是我跟哈里克一起离乐就没这事家
Herik will rise to every challenge
with courage and good sense
恰里克会勇敢面对每次挑
并且好好处理
Let's do the same
我们学学他吧
The Barbarian ship
is in sight, my lord.
蛮族人的船在视线范围内了
The Barbarian " ship
为人的国内
The Barbarian ship
is in sight, my, lord
般下蛮族人的船在视线范围内了
m
Well close in when night falls
天黑的时候我们会草过去
天黑的时候我们会靠过去
We'll close in when night falls
Prepare to board!
准备登船
And remember all we want
from that ship is the Shogi
同时记住我们只要从蛮族人船
抓到那个法师
画圣、
Y郑显Y董[巴回
6 oys au s! dIys ley山o
ueM aN‖ e Jaquays」pu
And remember, all we want
from that ship is the Shog
同时记住我们只要{蛮族人船
抓到那个师
or his book of tricks
或者得到他的生命之书就够了
… I always thought
you didn 't want me
我曾经以为是你不要我了
And now I've come
back to your ship,
现在我未受邀请却回到你的船上
uninvited, insisting
that you change your life
而且还坚持要你改变你们的生活方式
So Zek is right
I am like my mother.
西克说得没错我确实象我的母亲
n more ways than you know
甚至比你想象中更象
Except that you
won't betray me as she did
只要你不会跟你母亲那样背叛我
I can,t accept that
我不能接受
I cant believe she ever meant
any harm to the People of the Sea
我不相信她曾动过对海上一族不利的念头
Something has
happened, I'm sure of it
肯定是发生什么事
l'd like to know too
我也想知道发生什么了
ship can be a
dangerous place, my boy.
船上可以是很危险的地方小鬼
To arms! To arms
Enemy ship closing in fast!
准备战斗准备战斗
敌人的船正在快速靠近
Here they come!
他们来了
g6
Theyre turning back! We've done it
他们逃回去了我们A了
Where's Herik?
哈里克在哪
He must be hiding somewhere!
他肯定藏起来了
No. that's not like him
不可能那不是他的作风
There! They,re taking Herik
在那里他们把哈里克抓走了
Their attack was a diversion!
他们的攻击只是用来分散我们的注意
Herik
哈里克
Too late
太晚了
Cut the ropes!
We've g
ot to catch them
砍断船绳我们得追上他们
For this Shogi we risk everything
为了这个法师我们不惜冒一切风险
Now cut the ropes!
现在砍断船绳
We are assem bled here
我们聚集在这里
to determine the owners
of this sack of grain
是为了决定这袋谷子的归属
The evidence has been
presented and the witnesses heard
证据已经呈上请证人听判
Princess Djana
peer of the realm
裘娜公主这位王室贵族
will now render her most
just and merciful verdict
现在要宣读她最公证仁慈的判决
When"are you going to
rescue her from this mess
你什么时候去帮她解困啊
Experience is the
best teacher, Silkar.
经验是最好的老师塞尔卡
I must admit that I can find
nothing conclusive about this case
我得承认我没能找到确凿的证
But I assure you
that this sack is mine
可我肯定那袋谷子是我的
Otherwise, I would never insist
否则我不会这么坚持
I work hard enough as it is
那是我辛苦劳动得来的
-You spend more time in
this tavern than in the field
你呆在这个酒馆的时间比
在地里劳作的时间还长呢
That's enough
够了
We will adjourn until tomorrow
我们延期明天
Then, after carefully
considering all the arguments
在仔细考虑你们所有理由后
will give you my verdict.
我会给你们一个判决
What will you do?
你要做什么去
I haven 't the faintest idea
我脑子里一片混乱
Oh, my head
噢我的头
Have a headache, little Shogi?
头疼吗小术士
Perhaps we can find a
remedy in your Book of Life
也许我们能在生命之书上找到解药
Bragan! N
布拉刚不行
The barbarians!
They came after us
是蛮族人他们追上来了
Fire! Fire
着火了着火了
Stand and fight
e still outnumber them!
站住准备战斗我们人数多过他们
eave him be!
放开他
I didn't think you
were so reckless, Barbarian
我没想到你会这么不顾一切后果蛮族人
Did you think I would allow yo
你认为我会让你不费吹灰之力
to kidnap my son without a fight?
就绑走我的儿子吗
see
明白了
I see
see
明白
It's the animals
instinct to protect his brood
是动物保护幼雏的本能
Look out
Ne'll meet again
我们会再见面的
We can't stay aboard any longer
我们不能再呆在船上了
The fire is out of control
火势失去控制了
So- Djana, has a good night's
sleep inspired any wisdom
表娜好睡眠有给你点么启发吗
Not really. Tara
thinkal could use your advice
没有塔拉我想你是不是能给我个建议
But that's your job
可那是你的活哦
The princes advise theking
亲王们给国王进谏
and make the laws
and enforce the laws.
然后制定法律井执行
But this is ridiculous
可这件事太可笑了
We ought to make
their lives easier.
我们是应该让他们生活更容易些
not- control every little thing
可牛不是连这样的小事也要管
可这样时小也要器
not control every little thing
可并不是连这样的小事也要管
吗代生这样单也要
I think you've
ust had an inspiration
我想你已经得到启发了
Why don't you
consult the village elders
为什么不去请教一下村里的老者呢
You all know these
men better than I do
你们都比我了解这些人
What do you think?
你们有什么想法
Aymond has a tendency to get
things confused in his head
艾满德有时候有点糊涂
Theo is a nice lad.
but he does exaggerate
产西欧是个好小伙不过有点言过其实
The sack-isn' t very hea
那袋谷子并不重
It likely belongs to
the old lady, Gervaise
应该是老妇人格蕾丝的
The barbarians
attack shook her up
蛮族人的攻击吓倒她了
She probably forgot to
retrieve it when they left
在蛮族人离开后她可能忘记去拿
But if everyone knew
why didn't someone say something
可既然大家都知道为什么没人告诉我
态
We would never
challenge a royal decision
我们永远不会挑战王室的决定
学
Tell everyone to
assemble in the square
叫大家到广场集
I never would
have escaped from Bragan
如果你不来救我
if you hadn't come for me
我绝不可能逃离布拉刚的控制
You are my son
你是我儿
You saved the
Book of Life as well!
你还救回了生命之书
-Amd it doesnit even look Damaged
看起来没有任何损坏
(暂
墨
Katryn
凯塞茵
Mother!
母亲
erk,my son,
ou hear this message
合里克我的儿子如果你听到这条口信
ifLy ya heeartitiasmmes sges
my son
if you hear this message.
哈里动我的儿子如果你听到这条口信
it is because my brother
the Shogi Master, A
那肯定是因为我的哥哥也就是大法以
has judged that you are
mature enough to know the truth
觉得你已经足够成熟可以承受真相了
I-wanted you to know why I took
the most painful decision of my life
一我希望你知道为什么我作出了
生中最痛苦的决定
Your father is
a great leader Herik
你父亲是一位伟大的首领哈里克
but his love for me cost him the
love and respect of his people
可他对我的爱让他失去
族人对他的爱戴和尊敬
They need their chief,
他的族人需要他
I hope he can find it
his heart to forgive me
我希望他能舶我的这片苦心原谅我
When you were born. the
Men of the Sea felt threatened
你出生后海上一族觉得害怕
change you would bring
他们害怕你的出生会带来任何改变
When- learned
a plot against
当我得知他们想加害手你
decided to take you
he- safest refuge I know
于是我决定带你去我所知道
最安全的地方
to the Shogis
也就是法师们所在的地方
for denying you your family
原谅我让你和家人分离
Please know that I love you
记住妈妈爱你
didnt know.
我不知道
didnt understand
我也不明白
All these years I-thought
that she ' fled out of cowardice
这些年我直以为她是害怕才逃走
a Now I see that
she had great courage
现在我才知道她多么勇敢啊
She sacrificed all she
had for the sake of my - people
为了我的族人她西性了她拥有的y切
From now on they
will honour her memory
从今以后我的族人会记住她以示敬重
I'll see to that
我会处理的
Just lead them
nto a better future
带领他们走向更好的未来
that's what Mother
would have wanted
那才是母亲希望看到的
And-lwillabe a link between the
Shogis and the People of, the Sea
以后我会是法师和海上枭雄沟通的纽带
as she was
就象她那样
走吧
Go!
你走吧
③角
Tell your friends
告
诉你的朋友们
they don't have to fear thre
People of the Sea anyelonger.
他们不用再害怕海上雄了
Cgrew-up in a world
that I thought was perfect
在一个自认为完美的世界里长
was aprincess
and had no worries
我是个公主生活无无虑
King Edwyn was good and
wise and his laws were just
艾德温国王很仁慈睿智也很公正
But after Edwyn died
-the Regent, changed all th
可自从他驾崩后摄政王改变
TBut after Edwyn died
就
But after Edwyn died
the- Regent changed all that
向自从他驾崩后摄政王改变了一切
Since then, I have fought to
bring justice back to-the kingdom
从那时候开始我为这个王国的正义而战
wBut it starts here, with all of you
战斗从这里开始和你们大家起
You can rely on the wisdom
kof your own village Elders
们可以依靠村里老者的智慧
to settle many of your problems
without outside interference
来解泱些内部问题不受外人干涉
and participate more fully
the life of the
e kingdon
并且和极关心王国的命运
It will make us all stronger
让我们大家都变得更强
Thank you, princess.
谢谢您公主殿下
Diana:Tara
表娜塔拉我回来
Herik
哈里克
Are you all right?
你还好吧
Never better, Djana
再好不过了悲哪
The People of the Sea are no
longer the enemies of the Kingdom
海上枭雄不再是王国的敌人了种
Wolf gave me his word on it
沃尔夫向我承诺过了
I'm-happy for you, Herik
真替你高兴哈里克
It seems you finally
have your-father aback
看样你终于认回父亲了
es, ara
的塔拉
Y
And one day
will- also find my mother.
而且总有天我也会找回我母亲
SCRIPT SUPERVISOR
ScrIPT surE KTISOR
5c2-LiE ruBEN
Execu o SOMI DITOR
ereCUTTYE STORI EDITOR
H
s⊥sLL
ouida xois a⊥n。axa
STOM DITO
SaUDe DeStuTT
STUDIO MKNKE
LOT
PRODUCTION IDMIM1STRITOR- TOC
PRODUCTIONS III
okI In sHot ncoxd HoNoo" dokYeIStNIwOY Hoiongoxd
Yw OtanI
UCT和聚:3" PRODUCTIoNS nIl
xODUGTIONAXMGER
3DMODELING
GRIBOuIuLe
D MODELING
IRI BOUILLE
∈R1 BOUILLE
GuSTO GESOST
CHIEN
PEoN
A2器
surekTtsoRs
≌xm
器
F PU
3DMODEl
SuPERTISORS
器如
6黑T
SOFTWIRE DEYELOPER
cG孟T
贤A:
C6 KKTL
MODeL
nummi ecE
MOTION CAPTURE
SIUICON STUDIO
SOrEr
CGCG INC
PRODUCER
CGC6 INC
execu
IHDY TSTO
CGC6INC
exEcu
HXN SRI
G197 kONsO
ODUCTTOH(Ge累
tHE
PRODUCTI
LYOUT c INIATION SUPERTISOR
LATouT c yessxTIeN SureRnsor
Lxou∝凳y器 SuPExTso
ayw M器H
aY IHO MLDN
xo3品oa
aD inon
suPervIsoR
eom和0数He
NETWORL XD
TON LUTRXTOR
6∝ pecIAL EFFECTS5ueso
帮8or
demi a stATE S TsSs Superisor
NETWORK KD
TNN热万6e
UISHTIM6 C SPE
提55reso
UGHT1N6 c
NeT TONTTRATO
s是界
tsUs suEnson
UJEHTIM6 C ST
提H
TS SUTERTLSOR
SureKYISOR
I RODRMUET
FELE
Ture DIToR
TOONCAN PRODUCTIONS XII
TOONCKN PRODUCTIONS XII
POST.PRO
eso翼
SouND EffecTs c eDITIN
C eDITH
距既
GDITIN
PE ITTE
RTN耗
YTR OPERTTORS
outITy COMTEOL IND CKEDITS
sLax
ERIT
QuKLITY CoN
CREDITS
UALT CON
REDNE
ITY
OLTNIQ8o0D
ECHNI
PRODUCTION ISSISTANT
RODUCTION SECRETARY
ROsEnne duTtons
RODUC
PRODUC
e etOH TELE OS
T CKNKDI-FRANCE CO PRODUCTIO
LE CO
DE LT CWEHITOSRT
x CKMKDK-FRANCE CO-FcoDucTio
wEHT:Rr〓{a
翻译：英语辅导频道
输入/时间轴/压制：harry159821/黑月
校对：